"Enslaved by warlocks.
Stay here till you roll two, four or..."
(Leonard:)She was mad at him.
(Leonard:)She was done with him,
the relationship was broken...
(Leonard:)...and I walked over there and I fixed it.
(Howard:)Boy, that story gets better
every time you hear it.
(Sheldon:)I thought the first two renditions
were far more compelling.
(Sheldon:)Previously, I felt sympathy
for the Leonard character.
(Sheldon:)Now I just find him
to be whiny and annoying.
(Leonard:)Just eat your tangerine chicken.
(Sheldon:)I'd love to,
but I don't have tangerine chicken.
(Penny:)Thank you so much
for your stupid advice.
(Raj:)Incredible.
(Raj:)You managed to screw up the screw-up.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Leonard(knocking and entering):)I'm back.
(Penny:)I'm sorry I yelled at you.
It's not your fault.